(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
待ってろよ
Wait for me!
あー！
Aaa!
お肉！
Meat!
あらあら
Ara ara
はーい
Hi/Okay
Yeah!
チョコ美体
Choco-bitai
チョコ〜
Choco~
待って待って待って
Wait wait wait
にゃー！
Nya!
(Laugh)
ガチで
Seriously
やだやだやだ〜
No no no!
どうも、ホロライブ二期生、悪魔の保健医、癒月ちょこです〜
Hello, I'm Hololive 2nd Gen's devilish health teacher, Yuzuki Choco.
お前何しとんじゃ！
What do you think you're doing?!
(Scream)
Thank you super chat, thank you very much.
ほら、豚、登って、頑張って、豚
Look, pigs, climb, do your best, pigs.
ほら、豚、こっちよこっち、どっち〜
Look, pigs, this way, this way. Which way?~
はい、はい、はい
Yes, yes, yes
なんだろう
I wonder what it is
何年やってると思ってるんですか？ えいっ！
How many years do you think I've been doing this? Take that!
先生に向かってなんですかその言葉遣いは。
What's with that tone of voice towards your teacher?
友達じゃないんですよ、いいですか？
We're not friends, you know. Got it?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね
Because I'm Yuzuki Choco-sensei.
おやべー、うわー！
Oh crap, uwaa!
おいしかったの〜
It was delicious~
あ、違う！ ダメ！ あー！
Ah, no! Stop! Aaa!
チョコしかおらん
There's only Choco.
また動いた！
It moved again!
またあいつ！
That guy again!
はい、いらっしゃいませ。
Yes, welcome.
チョコ診療所へようこそ
Welcome to the Choco Clinic.
二期生だよ。
I'm 2nd Gen.
なあ〜
Right?~
おやすみ〜
Goodnight~
あ〜おいし
Ah~ delicious
あ〜、いい天気
Ah~ such nice weather
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい
I want to take a nap in the school infirmary bed
ズル休み、許されない
Skipping classes is not allowed
保健室は神聖なの
The school infirmary is a sacred place
サボってる、ちょっとだけ
I'm skipping out, just a little bit
誰も来なきゃやる気出ない
I can't get motivated if nobody comes
ちょこちょこ、せんせーしょん、イェイ！
Choco-choco sensation, yay!
ちょこちょこ、せんせーしょん
Choco-choco sensation
このままじゃ私ダメみたい
It seems like I'm useless as I am
あ、起きなきゃ、ふー、あと一分
Ah, I have to wake up... phew... just one more minute
二回目のあくび、おやすみなさい
Second yawn... goodnight
ごめんなさい、もう少しだけ寝かせて先生モード
I'm sorry, let me sleep just a little longer, sensei mode
シャットダウン
Shutdown
夢見るふわふわ
Dreaming fluffy
ずっとこうして眠りたい
I want to keep sleeping like this forever
ありがとうポカポカ
Thank you for the warmth
ちょっと休憩してるだけ
I'm just taking a short break
油断大敵ね
Unpreparedness is my worst enemy
急に君が来るなんて
To think you'd come so suddenly
ねえどこか悪いの？
Hey, is something wrong?
何か期待しているのかな
Are you expecting something?
揺らぐ心、巡る感情
Swaying heart, cycling emotions
口どけ甘いセセーション
A sweet melting sensation
癒されたい、甘えていたい
I want to be healed, I want to be pampered
特等席のチョコせんせーしょん
The special seat Choco-sensation
君の視線、君の体温
Your gaze, your body temperature
わかってても恋は計れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured
元気なのに溜息しちゃう
I'm healthy but I keep sighing
もしやこれは恋の病
Could this be lovesickness?
胸がドキドキするまで動けないから
I can't move until my heart thumps
ときめき運んで来てね、My Cute
So please bring me excitement, My Cute
ズル休み、またしたの？
Did you skip out again?
保健室は神聖なの
The school infirmary is a sacred place
サボってた、ちょっとだけ
I was skipping out, just a little bit
やっぱり君にいてほしい
I really want you to be here
明日は週末、おやすみなんだよ
Tomorrow is the weekend, it's a day off
家飲み、最高！
Drinking at home, the best!
引きこもり、最高！
Staying indoors, the best!
もちろんノーメイク
Of course, no makeup
パジャマだったら白衣着ます
If I'm in pajamas, I'll put on a lab coat
さあ全てを見せて
Now show me everything
ちゃんと診断できないじゃん
Or I won't be able to give a proper diagnosis
何を隠してるの？
What are you hiding?
鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
I can hear the speed of your heartbeat
満ちて心、巡る熱を
Filled heart, the cycling heat
正常保てる現状外
Beyond the state where I can keep it normal
愛されたい、頼られたい
I want to be loved, I want to be relied upon
特等席のチョコせんせーしょん
The special seat Choco-sensation
君の重み、君の匂い
Your weight, your scent
わかっても愛は計れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured
大好きだから溜息しちゃう
I love you so much that I sigh
やっぱりそれは恋の病
It really is lovesickness
胸がドキドキするまで動けないから
I can't move until my heart thumps
ときめき運んで来てね、My Cute
So please bring me excitement, My Cute
魔界だって
In the underworld
この世界だって
In this world
みんな癒やしが必要だから
Because everyone needs healing
ちょこちょこ、せんせーしょん、イェイ！
Choco-choco sensation, yay!
絶対君をダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you rotten
揺らぐ心 巡る感情
口どけ甘いセッション
Fluctuating heart, circulating emotions
A session with a sweet melt-in-the-mouth feel
癒されたい 甘えていたい
頼り合って チョコセッション
I want to be healed, I want to be pampered
Leaning on each other, a Choco session
君の視線 君の体温
分かっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your body temperature
Even knowing those, love cannot be measured
元気なのにダメージしちゃう
もしかしてもう手遅れ？
Even though I'm fine, I'm taking damage
Could it be already too late?
でもドキドキするまで
動けないから
But until my heart starts racing
I won't be able to move
ときめき運んで今すぐで
So bring that excitement to me right now
チョコチョコセッション イェイ！
Choco Choco Session, Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to spoil you too
はい、ということで！
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026...
Alright, and with that!
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Festival 2026...
...始まりました！
...has begun!
見て見て！一曲目からちょこ、
生まれ変わりました！
Look, look! Right from the first song,
Choco has been reborn!
いや今日はね、原点回帰ということで...
Well, today, as a return to my roots...
...ちょこの、なんと保健室ステージだの！
...it's my, believe it or not, infirmary stage!
いやちょっと、保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって...
Well, the infirmary has also been reborn a bit...
...めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりました！
...and has become super cute!
セッションドラマとかできそうだよね！
It looks like we could do a session drama or something!
今日は、生まれ変わったニューちょこと...
Today, along with the reborn new Choco...
...素敵なね、ゲスト様をいっぱい呼んで、
ライブをしていくんだけど、その前に！
...I've invited many wonderful guests
to perform live, but before that!
みんなちょこのこと、もっと見たいよね！
Everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも、まだダメだよ。うん。
Oh, but, not yet. Yeah.
これから来るお二人に、
ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいました！
I've asked the two who are about to arrive
to do a photo session for Choco!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう。
Now then, let's call them out right away.
ノエル様、ラミィ様！
Noel-sama, Lamy-sama!
ちょこし！せーの！
Chocoshi! One, two!
ちょこ先生お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Choco-sensei!
ありがとう、嬉しい！
Thank you, I'm so happy!
うぇー、ということで今回はね、
この可愛い両手に花で、
Whoa, so this time, with these two
lovely flowers on either side of me,
可愛いお二人に、ちょっとね、
ちょこの撮影会をしていってもらおうと思うんですけど、
I'm going to have these two cute ladies
do a little photo session for Choco,
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします。
どっちから？
But first, please introduce yourselves.
Which of you will go first?
はい、えー、こんまるー！
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと！
Yes, uh, Konmaru! I'm Shirogane Noel
from Hololive 3rd Gen!
はい、ホロライブ5期生の顔面国宝、
雪花ラミィです！
And I'm Hololive 5th Gen's 'National Treasure Face',
Yukihana Lamy!
今日はよろしくお願いします！はーい！
Nice to meet you all today! Yes!
まあね、ちょっとちょこ先生の
本当に可愛くなったところを、
Well, in order to show off the really
cute parts of Choco-sensei,
ちょっと団長頑張って、攻めていこうと思いますので
よろしくお願いします。
I, the Commander, will do my best to take some bold
shots, so please look forward to it.
攻めて攻めて！ラミィも攻めるよね？
Go for it! Lamy, you'll take some bold ones too, right?
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Lamy is also going to try taking some shots
right on the edge!
いや、撮影会やるならちょっとね、
この二人を呼ぶしかないかなーと思って、
Well, I thought if I'm going to have a photo session,
I just had to call these two,
呼んじゃいました！嬉しい！
So I did! I'm so happy!
しかもしかも、ちょっと後で、
And, what's more, a bit later,
この三人からなんと、お知らせもあるみたいなので。
The three of us will actually have an announcement.
お知らせ！？何だろう、気になる！
An announcement!? I wonder what it is, I'm curious!
まあ撮影会の後で、皆様楽しみにしてて下さい。
Well, it'll be after the photo session,
so everyone please look forward to it.
楽しみだーい！
I'm looking forward to it!
それじゃあちょっと、こちらで撮影会よろしくお願いします。
Alright then, let's head over here
for the photo session.
はーい、行くぞー！
Okay, let's go!
お、なんかすごいとこ来たぞ！
Oh, we've come to somewhere amazing!
ねー、すごい！可愛い！
可愛いでしょ、可愛いでしょ。
Yeah, amazing! So cute!
It's cute, right? It's cute.
撮影会は、ちょこのここの診察室でやります！
The photo session will be held
here in Choco's diagnosis room!
わー、診察室だ！ちょこ先生の診察室。すげー！
Whoa, a diagnosis room! Choco-sensei's
diagnosis room. Awesome!
かわいい！かわいい！
So cute! So cute!
でしょうでしょう？
Right? Right?
でもさ、診察室だけどベッドは？ベッドどこ？
But even though this is an examination room, where's the bed? Where's the bed?
あ、あれ？なんかパネルもあるんだけど、あれ使う？
Oh, what's that? There's also a panel, do we use that?
あ、ちょこ、ここダメなものがあるけど…
Ah, Choco, there's something here that's not allowed...
え、これダメなの？
Eh, is this not allowed?
そこはあとのメン限で使うの。
I'm going to use that for the membership section later.
あ、なに？そうなの？メン限？メン限？
Ah, what? Really? Membership? Membership?
さてちょっとね、ベッドとかちょっと色々撮影会とかシチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなと思って。
So, I was thinking of doing some photo sessions and situation dramas with the bed and other things.
シチュエーションドラマ？！とんでもないことをしようとしてる！本当だよ！
Situation drama?! You're trying to do something crazy! You really are!
いえ、そうなんですよ。
Yes, that's right.
ま、ね、ま、それは置いておいて。
Well, anyway, let's put that aside for now.
あ、置くんだ。
Oh, you're putting it aside.
ちょっと今回は二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので、まずは…
This time, I'd like you two to take some photos, so first...
撮りますよ。よいしょ。
Let's take some photos. Here we go.
ラミィ様には…
For Lamy-sama...
カメラ！え、本格的な！すごいカメラ来た！
A camera! Eh, it's professional! A great camera is here!
そしてノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, we have this, ta-da!
何だいこれ？
What is this?
ちょこのギリギリを守るために特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
It's a mosaic stick specially made to protect Choco's risky parts!
特別！すげー！特別来た！モザイク！
Special! Amazing! A special one is here! Mosaic!
ボタンでこのモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい。
Apparently, you can change the coarseness of the mosaic with the button.
変えれるの？今めっちゃ粗くなってるから…
You can change it? It's really coarse now...
あ、本当、薄くできる！本当だ！
Oh, really, you can make it finer! It's true!
すげー、でも粗いほうがむしろいいまであるね、これ。
Amazing, but maybe the coarse one is even better, in a way.
確かに。OK、隠すや。これ大丈夫かなでも配信、ね、ちょっと守りますよ。
True. OK, I'll hide it. I wonder if this is okay for the stream, though. I'll protect you.
ちょこの配信を守ってください。頑張ります！頑張ります！
Please protect Choco's stream. We'll do our best! We'll do our best!
それでは撮影会スタート！イエーイ！
Now, let the photo session start! Yay!
まずやっぱ全身。そうだね、そうだよね。
First, a full-body shot. Right, exactly.
普通にこうね、ちょっとポーズ。いつものちょこ先の…こんな感じ。
Just a normal pose like this. The usual Choco-sen... Like this.
ああ！美しい！
Ah! Beautiful!
美しい！ああ、いいねいいね！
Beautiful! Ah, nice, nice!
え、かわいい！もうもうここちょっとまずいんじゃないの、ここ？
Eh, cute! Wait, isn't this part a bit bad? This part?
まずいかな？ああ、逆に？え、逆に？
Is it bad? Ah, on the contrary? Eh, on the contrary?
ちょっとちょっと、ノリノリなんですけど。まずいかな？ちょっとちょっとね。
Wait, wait, she's really into it. Is it bad? Just a little bit.
ちょっとここ揺れてるめっちゃ！あ、モザイクが！モザイクが追いついてない！
Wait, this part is shaking a lot! Ah, the mosaic! The mosaic can't keep up!
追いついてない！じゃ、ノエル様頑張って頑張って！え、こうやってね？こういう感じでね？
It can't keep up! OK, Noel-sama, do your best, do your best! Eh, like this? Like this, right?
うんうん。で、どんどんどんどん。
Yeah, yeah. And then, more and more.
ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてみいいかな？ジャンプ確かに。
Could you try jumping a little? Jumping, for sure.
すごいプルンプルン！わ！ヤバ！めっちゃヤバ！めっちゃヤバ！めっちゃヤバ！
It's so jiggly! Wow! Crazy! Really crazy! Really crazy! Really crazy!
アカンでしょこれ！アイアイアイおい！あら！あら！
This isn't allowed! Hey hey hey! Oh my! Oh my!
え、ちょっとせっかくだから椅子とかも座っちゃう？椅子？うん、椅子ねここにありますね。
Eh, since we're here, why don't you sit in the chair? The chair? Yeah, the chair is right here.
はーい、よいしょ。おーいいいね、かわいい！
Here we go. Oh, nice, cute!
なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。あ、ちょこね、そこが赤なの。
It's kind of bluish. Oh, Choco's, that part is red.
え？！ちょっとちょっとちょっと…ま…まずい…ありがとうございます！
Eh?! Wait, wait, wait... That's... risky... Thank you very much!
そこがね赤なの、これがね。ありがとうございます！そう！
That part is red, this one. Thank you very much! Yes!
大丈夫？あ、でも中見えてないからね。大丈夫です大丈夫です、セーフですね。
Is it okay? Ah, but you can't see inside. It's okay, it's okay, it's safe.
見えてないよ。守ってます、チャンネル守ってます！
You can't see it. I'm protecting it, I'm protecting the channel!
いいんじゃ、こうどんどんどんどん上を見てもらって。
Great, keep going, look up more and more.
あ、いいね！あら可愛い！
Ah, nice! Oh, how cute!
見えてる？見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
Can you see? I can see, I can see!
見えてる？あ、かわいい！かわいいね！おー！
Can you see? Ah, cute! So cute! Ooh!
え、ちなみにラミィさん。あれですよ、この椅子に座って先生ポーズも希望ですけど。
Eh, by the way, Lamy-san. I'd also like to see her sit in this chair and do a teacher pose.
あ、希望してますけど。先生ポーズ取ってほしい。先生ポーズってなんだ？
Ah, I'm hoping for it. I want her to do a teacher pose. What's a teacher pose?
こんな感じ？あ、いい！いいですね、いい！非常にいい！
Like this? Ah, nice! It's good, good! Extremely good!
もうモザイクいらないでこれは。非常に…非常にいらないのかこれ。
We don't even need the mosaic for this. Extremely... We really don't need it for this?
いや分かんない、分かんない。ちょこ先の魅惑が溢れすぎてて。
No, I don't know, I don't know. Choco-sen's charm is overflowing too much.
いいですね！素晴らしい！え、団長もいいですか？
It's good! Wonderful! Eh, Danchou, is it okay?
何何？え、お尻フリフリちょっとしていただきたいんでちょっと…フリフリ。
What, what? Eh, I'd like you to shake your butt a little... Shake, shake.
えっと、そう、後ろ向いてもらって。後ろ向いて…白衣越しだけど。
Um, yeah, turn around. Turn around... Even through the lab coat.
フリフリ。あ、いいね！フリフリ。白衣越しだが…
Shake, shake. Ah, nice! Shake, shake. It's through the lab coat, but...
その下に…その…あ、ちょっとその下に…スカート結構際どい。
Underneath that... That... Ah, wait, underneath that... The skirt is quite risky.
でもこれ、うん、白衣ってこれ、脱ぎ…脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
But this, yeah, the lab coat, take it... I want you to take it off, but can't you take it off?
脱げるけどメン限でって言ってた。あ、メン限なら脱いでくれるんですね！
I can, but I said I would in the membership section. Ah, so you'll take it off in the membership section!
あ、いい！え、ガニ股…あの、ココ会長リスペクトで団長ガニ股好きなんで。
Ah, nice! Eh, bow-legged... Um, out of respect for Coco-kaichou, Danchou likes bow-legged poses.
うわあ！すごい！ガニ股さん！あ、いいね！
Whoa! Amazing! Bow-legged-san! Ah, nice!
ガニ股助かる！ガニ股！これちょっとモザイクモザイク！
Bow-legged is a lifesaver! Bow-legged! Wait, mosaic, mosaic!
ちょ、見えてるもんな！モザイクお願いします！モザイクがむしろ逆効果か…
Wait, you can see it! Mosaic, please! Actually, the mosaic might be counterproductive...
ちょ、やばい！逆にやばい！やばいやばいやばいやばいやばいやばい！
Wait, it's bad! On the contrary, it's bad! Bad bad bad bad bad bad!
かわいい！ふぅー！どんどん行こうどんどん行こう！
Cute! Whew! Let's keep going, let's keep going!
えっと…じゃ、ラストはやっぱアイドルだからさ、ちょこ先。アイドル。飛びきりのかわいいアイドルお願いします。
Um... Well, for the last one, since you're an idol, Choco-sen. An idol. An exceptionally cute idol pose, please.
アイ！え、かわいい！や、これは…あ、いいね！ルピス！
Hi! Eh, cute! Wow, this is... Ah, nice! Peace!
かわいい！
So cute!
アップいい！顔のアップいい！
The close-up is great! The face close-up is nice!
たまらんです！
I can't take it!
かわいい！
So cute!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
いやちょっとね、この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので...
Well, we'll continue the rest in the member-only stream...
♡このあとのメン限♡ アフターライブ 特別撮影会 シチュエーションドラマ2本
♡Next Member-only Stream♡ After-live, Special photo session, 2 Situation dramas
メン限では、歌も撮影会もシチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やっちゃいます！
In the member-only stream, we'll do songs, a photo session, and even two situation dramas!
おー！楽しみだ！
Oh! Looking forward to it!
えー、ちなみにさ、なんかタイトルとかあんの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, are there titles for those situation dramas?
あ、今回のタイトルがー...
Ah, the titles this time are...
先生とベッドで特別バレンタインー！
Special Valentine with Sensei in Bed!
特別？！先生とベッドで？！特別バレンタイン？！
Special?! With Sensei in bed?! Special Valentine?!
っていうタイトルとー、あと、診察室で甘い処方箋をーっていう...
That title, and also, "Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room"...
あー！甘い！甘い！
Ah! Sweet! Sweet!
♡シチュエーションドラマ♡ 先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン 診察室で甘い処方箋を
♡Situation Dramas♡ Special Valentine with Sensei in Bed / Sweet Prescription in the Examination Room
あの、目線も、ちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて...
The perspective will be like, the cameraman is lying on the bed...
ちょっとみんなが本当に、チョコが覆い被さるように、ちょっと...
So that everyone can see Choco leaning over them, kind of...
おー！たまらん！見たい見たい！
Oh! Irresistible! I want to see it!
いろんな画角で撮っていきたいと思います。
I want to shoot from various angles.
えー、楽しみだ！楽しみだー！
Looking forward to it!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ということでそろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います！
So, time is running out, let's get back to the live performance!
こんな気持ちでライブだった！
I'm in the mood for the live now!
そうです！
That's right!
急げ！
Hurry!
はーい！というわけで...
Yes! So...
この後お二人それぞれデュエットしてもらうんだけど...
After this, each of you will perform a duet with me...
ちょっとね、最後に3人でも歌うので楽しみにしといてください！
And finally, the three of us will also sing together, so please look forward to it!
楽しみ！お楽しみにー！
Excited! Look forward to it!
それでは次に行きましょうか！
Shall we move on to the next one?
あ、これ？
Ah, this?
そう！リボンも付いてる！かわいい！
Yes! It has ribbons too! Cute!
じゃあちょっとカーテンの裏でお着替え行ってきます！
Well, we're going behind the curtain to change!
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer chocolate
そろそろその身 ベイビー
It's almost time, baby
とろけちゃってキャッチミー ダーリン
Melt and catch me, darling
ピュアピュア ココア ふわり
Pure pure cocoa, softly
ゆるゆる ワンツー
Loosely, one two
なんか眠れない夜には
On nights when I can't sleep
お散歩 特別なパーティタイム
Take a walk, a special party time
二人きり やったー
Just the two of us, yay!
あの角曲がれば 電柱しかない公園だよ
Turn that corner and it's a park with only utility poles
蒸し暑い空気の中 迷い込むんだ
Getting lost in the humid air
コンビニ ちょっと寄り道
Stopping by the convenience store
買い出し アイスじゃなくてこれがいい
Buying stuff, not ice cream, this is what I want
肝臓 お酒 ほろ酔い ウインクで ストロング
Liver, alcohol, tipsy, a wink makes it strong
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラムで潰してお願い
Liqueur isn't enough to get drunk anymore, please knock me out with rum
お砂糖 マシマシで 飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra extra sugar, I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして ゴクッと飲んで
In the scorching heat, melt it and take a gulp
癖のある私のこと 大事にしてよね
Take good care of me, with all my quirks
サマーチョコレート そろそろその身 ベイビー
Summer chocolate, it's almost time, baby
とろけちゃってキャッチミー ダーリン
Melt and catch me, darling
ピュアピュア ココア ふわり
Pure pure cocoa, softly
ゆるゆる ワンツー
Loosely, one two
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
A slightly lonely way home
フラフラ 特別ボーナスタイム
Staggering, special bonus time
手を繋ごう イェーイ
Let's hold hands, yay!
大きめ Tシャツ 君に借りた ありがとうね
A large T-shirt borrowed from you, thank you
匂わせみたいにして 困らせたいんだ
I want to tease you, like I'm leaving a hint
コンビニ また寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しい もう一本だけ 弱いやつ
Having fun, just one more, the weak one
ツルツルリ メルティ
Slippery, slippery, melty
テンパリングが大事
Tempering is what's important
暑すぎても飽きちゃって
If it's too hot, I'll get tired of it
冷たいのはダメ やだもん
Too cold is no good, I don't want that
チョコみたいな私を
Take me, who's like chocolate
プレシャスにして扱って
And treat me like I'm precious
炭酸のお酒で
With a carbonated drink
シュワシュワシュワ
Fizz, fizz, fizz
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach if you don't express it
恋してるチョコに
To the chocolate in love
ここでチュッとして
Give it a kiss right here
夜空のグラスに
Into the glass of the night sky
キラキラこぼして
Spill the sparkles
息もできないくらいに
So much that I can't even breathe
もうだって だって だって だって
Already because, because, because, because
恋に溺れて
Drowning in love
君の熱で溶けたら
If I melt from your heat
そのまんまで食べてよ
Eat me just as I am
手にベトベトついちゃって
Getting all sticky on your hands
一生一緒
Together for a lifetime
甘いお酒 ほろ酔い
Tipsy from the sweet alcohol
ウインクでストロング
Strong with a wink
リキュールじゃあ酔えない
I can't get drunk on liqueur
ラブで尽くして お願い
Shower me with love, please
お砂糖マシマシで
With extra sugar
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱さ溶かして
Melt away the scorching heat
ゴクッと飲んで
Drink it all down
癖のある私だからさ
Since I'm a bit quirky
君が選ばれた
You were the one chosen
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ドロドロトロリベイビー
Melt, melt, melty baby
とろけちゃって キャッチ ミー ダーリン
Melting away, catch me darling
ピュアピュア ココアふわり
Pure, pure cocoa floating
クルクル ワン ツー
Spinning around, one two
What's up Japan!
Can you hear me?
It's reggaeton time!
No money, no joy.
Two smart bunnies.
There is no reason to be down.
It's time to get up!
We have a hot new song.
That's from AKB48.
To make you feel good.
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie.
So dance Japan crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie
あなたのこと好きなのに
Even though I like you
私には興味ない
You have no interest in me
何度目かの失恋の準備
Getting ready for yet another heartbreak
Yeah Yeah Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の
If I look around, there's so many
可愛い子たちがいるんだもん
Cute girls everywhere
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You won't notice a plain flower
Yeah Yeah Yeah!
カフェテリアに流れるMusic
Music flowing in the cafeteria
ぼんやり聴いていたら
Listening to it idly
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
Without realizing, I'm matching the rhythm
つま先から動き出す
Starting to move from my toes
止められない今の気持ち
I can't stop these feelings right now
Come on come on come on come on baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
A Fortune Cookie in love
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't so bad
Hey Hey Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To call in luck, show a smile
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
A heart-shaped Fortune Cookie
運勢今日よりもよくしよう
Let's make our luck better than today's
Hey Hey Hey! Hey Hey Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't so bad, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
An amazing miracle will happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling we'll love each other somewhere
あなたに夢中　心振り向かせたい
I'm crazy about you, I want to make your heart turn my way
だけど自分に自信がないの
But I have no confidence in myself
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can imagine your reaction
Yeah Yeah Yeah...
性格いい子がいいなんて
Saying that you like girls with good personalities
男の子は言うけれど
Boys always say that, but...
ルックスがアドバンテージ
Looks are an advantage
いつだって可愛い子が
Cute girls always...
人気投票1位になる
...come first in popularity polls
Please Please Please Oh Baby　私も見つめて
Please Please Please Oh Baby, look at me too
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Love Fortune Cookie
その殻　さあ壊してみよう
Come on, let's try breaking its shell
Hey Hey Hey...
先の展開　神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know what's coming next
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie of Tears
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative
Hey Hey Hey　世界は愛で溢れているよ
Hey Hey Hey, the world is overflowing with love
悲しい出来事　忘れさせる
Making us forget the sad things
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
I think tomorrow the wind of tomorrow will blow
Come on Come on Come on Baby　占ってよ
Come on Come on Come on Baby, tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Love Fortune Cookie
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future isn't that bad
Hey Hey Hey...
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To call for luck, you have to show a smile
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
The Heart Fortune Cookie
運勢今日より良くしよう
Let's make our luck better than today
Hey Hey Hey　人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Hey Hey Hey, life isn't something to throw away, right?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling we'll fall in love somewhere
君が好きったら君が好き！
If I say I like you, I like you!
あのね乙女は本気出すとすごいんです
You know, a maiden is amazing when she gets serious
ワンツーいずれしゅっしゅ　あの手この手で
One, two, eventually dash! Using this way and that way...
ライバルを出し抜くの　全部計算済み
To outwit my rivals, it's all calculated
レシピ通り
Just like the recipe
武器だって武器にしちゃって
Making even my weapons into weapons
塞いでみたりして
Trying to block you
酔ったフリで甘えて
Acting drunk and being sweet
ついでにぶっちゅ
And then, a smooch
あ、寝坊した
Ah, I overslept!
つまみ食いしたらなくなった！
I snacked on it and now it's gone!
ブランデーに日本酒
Brandy and Sake
時にファンキー
Sometimes funky
苦いのはNGで
Bitter things are a no-go
女の子の季節だもん
It's the girls' season, after all
全部思い通りになってよね
Everything should go exactly as I want
君は私と結ばれます
You will be tied to me
本命あげちゃう メルティ
I'll give you my true feelings, Melty
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
I won't give you to anyone, The Great War
ときめいちゃいます メルシー
My heart is fluttering, Merci
それじゃテコでも動かない 内緒のデート
A secret date that won't move even with a lever
Sweety Sweety Kiss
甘くていいの
Sweet is fine
Sweety Sweety Heart
こういうのが一番
Being in love is the best
初恋なんだもん　絶対譲らない
It's my first love, I'll never give it up
覚悟です　本気なのです
I'm prepared, I'm serious
目を見て言って　君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me your feelings
Girls Battle Field!
誰これと喋ってんの
Who are you talking to?
Girls Battle Field!
意思疎通がショート
Our communication is short-circuiting
Girls Battle Field!
大丈夫　へこたれないもん
It's okay, I won't lose heart
惚れさせた方が勝ちです
The one who makes the other fall in love wins
鼻血が出るほど食べちゃいな
Eat until you get a nosebleed
砂糖の量は愛の量
The amount of sugar is the amount of love
間違えた これ塩だった
Wait, I made a mistake, this was salt
マーベラス
Marvelous!
ドキドキドキドキしている
My heart is thumping
真心込めてラッピング
Wrapping it with all my heart
自分も本気モードでいく
I'm going in serious mode too
祈る ラブリー チャンス
Praying for a lovely chance
何度もし作成した 予行練習もした
I've practiced and prepared so many times.
夜明けになどなるな 大丈夫自分史上 一番可愛い私なんだから
Don't let the dawn come. It's okay, I'm the cutest version of myself ever.
君は私と結ばれます
You and I will be tied together.
結ばれる運命なのです
It's our destiny to be tied together.
本命あげちゃうメルティー 誰にも渡さない大戦争
I'll give you my true feelings, Melty. A great war where I won't give you to anyone.
トキメいちゃいますメルシー それじゃ手とか繋いじゃいな内緒デート
I'm feeling excited, Merci. Then, let's hold hands and go on a secret date.
Chu-ki Chu-ki Kiss 甘くていいの
Chuki chuki kiss, it's okay to be sweet.
Chu-ki Chu-ki Hug こういうのが一生
Chuki chuki hug, this is for a lifetime.
初恋なんだもん 絶対譲らない覚悟です 本気なのです
Because it's my first love. I'm prepared to never give you up. I'm serious.
目を見て言って 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me your feelings.
Piura-piura Piura-piura Piura-piura Piura-love...
はい！ということで、チョコたち3人の新曲でしたー！
Yes! And so, that was our new song from the three of us!
イエーイ！新曲でしたー！
Yay! It was a new song!
改めて、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にですね、コラボ歌唱した『初恋大戦争』という新曲なんですけど
Once again, it's our new collaboration song with Noel-sama and Lamy-sama called "Hatsukoi Daisensou".
今回、作詞作曲をめだんし様、そして編曲を洋介様にお願いいたしまして
For this song, we asked Medansy-sama for lyrics and composition, and Yo-ke-sama for the arrangement.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今回のテーマがバレンタインの日に3人の可愛い女の子たちが1人の男の子を手に入れるために
The theme this time is three cute girls on Valentine's Day, trying to win over one boy...
バチバチにですね、出し抜き合おうとするみたいな
...and aggressively trying to outmaneuver each other.
なるほど！
I see!
激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております！
It's a super sweet theme song!
いいね、可愛い！
Nice, so cute!
そう。いやもう3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので
Yes. With our three voices together, it's become a total idol song.
ぜひぜひ皆様聴いてください！
Everyone, please give it a listen!
聴いてねー！
Please listen!
えー、何回も聴きたいなー！
I want to listen to it over and over!
ねー、何回も聴きたい。どこで聴けるんですか？
Right, I want to listen many times. Where can we hear it?
こちらの楽曲はこの後24時から、2月15日0時からですね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
This song will be available on various music sites starting from 24:00 tonight, February 15th at 0:00!
やったー！
Hooray!
聴けるー！
We can listen to it!
そしてですね、え？この配信後すぐにこの楽曲のMVが！
And then, what? Immediately after this stream, the MV for this song...
やったー！公開されます！
...will be released! Yay!
ぜひぜひ皆様いっぱい聴いて、MVの方にもちょっと感想とかね、コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなーって思います！
Please listen to it a lot, and I'd be happy if you could leave some thoughts and comments on the MV!
お願いしますー！
Please do!
じゃあね、2人とも今日はありがとう！
Well then, thank you both for today!
お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうー！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
引き続きね、頑張ってください！
Good luck with the rest of the stream!
頑張ってね！ありがとう！
Do your best! Thank you!
ほな、おさらばじゃ！
Well then, farewell!
おさらば！
Farewell!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そしてここからライブ後半となります！
And now we're moving into the second half of the live concert!
まだまだゲストパートとか、なんと最後に重大告知もあるので
There are still guest parts and, what's more, a major announcement at the end...
皆様、一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
...so everyone, let's have fun together!
それでは、次のゲストはこちら！
Now then, here is the next guest!
大人なフリして。
Otona na Furi Shite.
急に会いたいって いつものように準備してる 午前1時過ぎの終電で向かうって返した
You say you want to meet suddenly. I'm preparing as usual. I replied that I'll head over on the last train after 1 AM.
やめときなよって言われてもまた 会いに行く会いたいから
Even if I'm told to stop, I'll go see you again, because I want to see you.
大人なフリして。
Pretending to be an adult.
ベランダに落ちちゃう
Falling onto the balcony
街の風は少し冷たい
The city breeze is a little cold
慣れないワイン無理やり飲み干してしまってはフラフワ
I force myself to drink unfamiliar wine, then I feel lightheaded
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手にしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess things up?
少し見逃したくない
I don't want to miss a single moment
ちょっと期待してね
Expect a little from me
ずっと見栄張ってね
Always keep putting on appearances
周りばかり気にして生きてる
I live my life constantly worrying about everyone around me
ちょっと優越感でも
Even with a little sense of superiority
なんか寂しくてあぁ
I feel somewhat lonely, ah
本当は自分じゃない気がして
I feel like it's not actually me
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending I understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
When it's not like that at all, I force myself
味のしないキスをしても やっぱり一番嬉しくて
Even when we kiss and it feels empty, it's still what makes me happiest
取り繕った私は可愛いかな
I wonder if the 'me' I've polished up is cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I fall apart
何も消えそうな糸で繋がってる恋だね
Our love is held together by a thread that seems like it might vanish
私が諦めたらきっと簡単に消えちゃうね
If I give up, it'll surely disappear so easily
引き止めるにはどうする？
What should I do to make you stay?
溢れ出したらどうする？
What should I do if it all spills out?
不器用指先絡めて
Clumsy fingertips intertwined
いつもチェックしてね
Always keep checking on me
息を切らしてね
Keep being out of breath
他の子と比べてばかりいた
I was always comparing myself with other girls
一番見てほしいあぁ
I want you to look at me the most, ah
目の前の貴方はあぁ
But you, right in front of me, ah
どこか違う景色見てる
Are looking at some other scenery
いつは優しいフリして
Always pretending to be kind
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
When it's not like that at all, laughing
近づけば近づくほど心は遠く感じて
The closer I get, the further away your heart feels
少しずつ離れてやっと分かるよ
Pulling away little by little, I finally understand
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I forget everything
自分はもっと強ければさよならを言えるのにあぁ
If only I were stronger, I could say goodbye, ah
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending I understand
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
When it's not like that at all, I force myself
ふと見せる優しさがずっと忘れられなくて
I can't ever forget the kindness you occasionally show
取り繕った私は可愛いかな
I wonder if the 'me' I've polished up is cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I fall apart
そして溢れ出したあぁ 私は頑張ったよね
And then it overflowed, ah, I really did my best, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると思っていた もういいから
I thought you'd look back at me someday, but it's okay now
取り繕った私は流れていく
The 'me' I've polished up is being washed away
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight, hold me until I forget everything
chocolate box
作詞・作曲：dezzy (一二三)
Lyrics/Music: dezzy (Hifumi)
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always seem somewhat sleepy
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
You always seem somewhat bored
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
You always seem somewhat troubled
なんかいつもスマホ弄ってるし
You're always fiddling with your smartphone
ホントはテンション高いのに
You're usually so high-spirited
アタイと居るときゃ低いし
But you're so down when you're with me
なんの自分ありえなくない？
How can you be like that? No way!
キライ大嫌いどーでもいい！
I hate you, I really hate you! Whatever!
だったら僕も言うけどさ
Well then, I'll say it too
ちっちゃな事ですぐ怒るし
You get mad over tiny little things
いっぱいしたらすぐ泣くし
And you start crying right away if I do too much
ゴメンって言っても許してくれないし
And even if I say sorry, you won't forgive me
そのわりにゃ気が付きゃいれば
But despite that, when I notice you
手を繋ごうとか言うし
You're saying things like, 'Let's hold hands'
あぁなんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are
ちくしょーもう知らないぞ！
Darn it! I don't care about you anymore!
甘い甘い恋の魔法は
The sweet, sweet magic of love
紅茶味の秘密のチョコレート
Is a secret black tea-flavored chocolate
2人だけのデコレーションを
A decoration for just the two of us
散りばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
Shall we scatter it, color it, and eat it up?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
A mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたならきっと
If we warm it up and mix it, I'm sure
いつかお口に合う味になるの
It will one day become a taste that suits your palate
ねーねー チョコいいだな
Hey, hey, Choco is nice, isn't she?
なんで？
Why?
さっきは あのね ごめんね
About earlier, um, sorry.
何が？
For what?
いつも モヤッてなるじゃん
You know how it always gets hazy.
それで？
And?
今日は これを渡したくて
I wanted to give you this today.
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Because words aren't enough.
だから
So...
受け取ってくれないかな
Could you please accept it?
何よ！
What is it?!
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me.
ワー！
Whoa!
何だよそれ
What was that?
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃう
I end up depending on your kindness without thinking
誰よりも近いから 素直になれない
Because we're closer than anyone, I can't be honest
君の一生懸命さ ついつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting how hard you try
誰よりも一番 大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone else
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure box of dreams
奇跡味の代償のチョコレート
A chocolate that is the price of a miracle's taste
2人だけのイノベーションを
An innovation for just the two of us
探し組み立てたら賑やか
If we find and assemble it, it'll be lively
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter vanity box of daily life
世界味の代償のチョコレート
A chocolate that is the price of the world's taste
冷めきって割れないように
So that it doesn't cool down and break
大事に包んで生涯の完成まで
Wrap it carefully until the completion of a lifetime
いつだって
Always
やめるときも
Even when we stop
どんなときも
No matter when
そうずっと
Yes, forever
健やかなるときも
Even in health
手を取って
Take my hand
違う2人を分かつまで
Until it parts us, two different people
愛してる
I love you
僕もそうさ
Me too
そばにいて
Stay by my side
そばにいる
I am by your side
なんて嘘かもよ
That might be a lie, though
はぁ、そうか
Oh, I see
僕も適当に言った
I just said it randomly too
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet
苦い苦い
Bitter, bitter
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
A secret chocolate with the taste of the universe
2人だけのデコレーションを
A decoration for just the two of us
散りばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
Shall we scatter it, color it, and eat it up?
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
A mysterious chocolate with the taste of the future
温めて混ぜたなら絶対に
If we warm it up and mix it, absolutely
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
It will one day become the most happy taste
いっせーので
On the count of three
Thank you so much! See next time!
Thank you so much! See you next time!
ねぇ一つだけ聞いていい？私のこと
Hey, can I ask you just one thing? About me
告白日和、です！
It's a perfect day for a confession!
会えるかな今日は 心が騒いで
I wonder if I can meet you today, my heart is racing
好きってしたくなった ときめき踊る瞬間
I wanted to say I love you, the moment my heart skips a beat
私のことなど たぶん気にしてないのだけど
You probably don't care about me, but
ここにいるんだよ 私はここよ
I'm right here, I'm right here
自信が揺れ動く 嫌われてないかな
My confidence wavers, I wonder if you hate me
勢いでとにかく 挨拶だ！
Anyway, with momentum, let's greet you!
やっと晴れたね ぱっと晴れたね
It's finally cleared up, it's suddenly cleared up
そして元気になれ
And then, cheer up
おはようの代わりに 背中を叩いて
Instead of saying 'good morning', I'll pat you on the back
さぁ行くよ
Here we go
やっと晴れたら ぱっと晴れたら
If it finally clears up, if it suddenly clears up
きっと元気な笑顔
Surely, a cheerful smile
なんだか今のこの気持ちが せつなくなったよ
Somehow, this feeling right now has become painful
授業は上の空 遠くを眺めたい
My mind is elsewhere during class, I want to gaze into the distance
恋って甘いもんじゃない
Love isn't something sweet
切なさもください半分
Give me half of the pain too
目で見るだけでいい
Just looking is enough
触って確かめなきゃだから
Because I have to touch and make sure
動き出そうよ　自分らしくね
Let's start moving, in our own way
楽しく生きるの
Living happily
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle
言わずに悔やむより勇気出そう
Better to be brave than to regret not saying anything
ずっと前から　うんと前から　聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you for a long, long time
私から　最初に
From me, first
伝えてしまえ　大好きです
I'll just say it: "I love you!"
ずっと前だよ　うんと前だよ　聞いたことに答えて
It was a long, long time ago; answer what you heard
どんなふうに感じてるの
How are you feeling?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything
楽しく生きるの
Living happily
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle
本当は不安でも勇気出そう
Even if I'm actually anxious, I'll be brave
いこうよ！
Let's go!
うん！
Yeah!
ずっと前から　うんと前から　聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you for a long, long time
私から　最初に
From me, first
伝えてしまえ　大好きです
I'll just say it: "I love you!"
ずっと前だよ　うんと前だよ　聞いたことに答えて
It was a long, long time ago; answer what you heard
どんなふうに感じてるの
How are you feeling?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything
世界は恋に落ちている　光の矢　胸を射す
The world is in love; an arrow of light pierces my heart
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you
ねえ　教えて
Hey, tell me
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is in love
作詞・作曲: HoneyWorks
Lyrics & Composition: HoneyWorks
すれ違う言葉に　ちょっとだけの後悔
A little regret over words that missed their mark
涙こぼれて
Tears overflow
忙しい感情　鼓動にリンクする
Frantic emotions link to my heartbeat
チューニング
Tuning
確かめたいんだ
I want to make sure
目標ばかりに　とらわれて
Only focused on goals
大事なものが　霞んで逃げて
Important things grew hazy and escaped
今日もリスタート
Restarting again today
世界は恋に落ちている　光の矢　胸を射す
The world is in love; an arrow of light pierces my heart
全部わかりたいんだよ　ねえ
I want to understand everything, hey
聞かせて
Let me hear it
たった1ミリが遠くて
A mere millimeter feels so far
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days I ran through
忘れない　忘れられない
Won't forget, can't forget
輝く1ページ
That shining page
お似合いの二人に
To a well-matched pair
なんだか複雑な気持ちがいるよ
I have somewhat complicated feelings
初めての感情　鼓動にリンクする
This new feeling links to my heartbeat
体温計
A thermometer
こぼれちゃったかな
I wonder if it spilled out
自分のことはわからないまま
While still not understanding myself
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even went as far as giving advice to that girl
胸が痛いや
My chest hurts
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my heart
気付いたこの想いは
These feelings I've realized...
もう遅いの
...are already too late
あの子の方が可愛いの知ってるよ
I know she's cuter than me
だけど
But...
うまくいかないでなんてね
Thinking "I hope it doesn't work out"...
逃げ出したいくせに
...even though I want to run away
「バカ、君のこと全部分かりたいって思っちゃう」
"Dummy, I find myself wanting to understand everything about you"
「これが恋だって初めて気づいたの」
"I realized for the first time that this is love"
「絶対振り向いてほしい」
"I definitely want you to look my way"
「遅かったけど、あきらめたくない。だって、好きだから。」
"It was late, but I don't want to give up. Because I love you."
春に咲いた花が恋をした
The flower that bloomed in spring fell in love
花は必死に上を向いて笑った
The flower desperately looked up and smiled
青い夏のつぼみも恋をした
The bud of the blue summer also fell in love
咲かない花と火薬の匂い
A flower that won't bloom and the smell of gunpowder
本当の気持ち言葉にして
Putting my true feelings into words
大切なこと話せたら
If only I could talk about the important things
今日もリスタート
Today is a restart as well
鈍感な君だから
Because you're dense,
口に出して言わなきゃ
I have to say it out loud
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you right now
「ねぇ、好きです」
"Hey, I love you"
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射す
An arrow of light pierces my heart
全部分かりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything
「ねぇ、聞かせて」
"Hey, let me hear it"
たぐり寄せて、もうゼロセンチ
Pulling you closer, now zero centimeters
駆け抜けた日々に
In the days we ran through
忘れない、忘れられない 輝く１ページ
I won't forget, I can't forget, one shining page
はい！ということで、ここまでは、
Yes! So, up until now,
アキ様、ロボ子、ござるに、ふーたと一緒に
I sang along with Aki-sama, Roboco, Gozaru, and Flare.
歌わせていただきました。
Thank you for listening.
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
さてさて、ここからは、なんと
Now then, from here, would you believe
重大告知が、２つあります！
I have two major announcements!
まず１つ目が、こちら！
First is this!
ドドン！癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2026グッズ！
Dodon! Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods!
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to introduce them in detail.
まずは、こちら！ちょこのクッション！
First is this! Choco's Cushion!
いやこれね、いやちょっとちょこの誕生日といえば、
Well, speaking of Choco's birthday,
毎年Nardack先生ありがとうございますということで、
every year I have to say thank you to Nardack-sensei.
今年もNardack先生にめちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました。
This year too, Nardack-sensei drew an incredibly wonderful illustration.
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで、
The theme this year is Valentine's,
ちょっとね、チョコメイトを抱きながら、
so I made it a chocolate-style cushion
ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました。
while holding a Chocomate.
可愛いでしょ？サイズ感がちょうど、
Cute, right? The size is just about right
枕くらいになってるので、
for a pillow,
ちょっとねお昼寝の時とか仮眠用に、スヤァってできる、感じで使えちゃいます。
so you can use it to take a quick nap.
そして続いては、こちら！
And next is this!
なんと、今回初めてちょっとお菓子が作れる、
Wow, for the first time, you can actually make sweets with...
なんと、チョコのチョコレート型！
Choco's chocolate mold!
耐熱も冷却も、あったかいのも冷たいのも両方使えちゃって、
It's heat-resistant and can be cooled, so you can use it for both hot and cold things.
ちょっとね、チョコレートチョコメイトの今回はチョコレート型になっております。
This time, it's a chocolate mold for the 'Choco-mates'.
ま、マフィンとかね、クッキーとか、
Well, you can use it for muffins, cookies,
あとはま、普通に冷やし固めてチョコレート入れたりとか、
or just cooling down chocolate.
なんか色々使えるからぜひ、みんなも作ってみてね！
It has many uses, so please try making something!
そして続いてはこちら！ お待たせしました！
And next is this! Thank you for waiting!
チョコのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Choco's Peaceful Sleeping Plushie Keychain Holder!
ま、チョコといえばね、睡眠ということで、超ロングスリーパーのチョコが、
Well, speaking of Choco, it's all about sleep. So the super long-sleeper Choco is...
今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって、ちょっとすやすやぬいぐるみで、作らせていただきました。
now a plushie keychain. I made this 'peaceful sleeping' plushie.
ま、ずっとね、肌身離さず持っていればいつか寝息聞こえてくるかもしれない！
If you keep it with you all the time, you might hear some sleeping sounds one day!
そして！今年もございます！癒月チョコ書き下ろし台本の、耳なめASMR台本！
And! We have it again this year! An ear-licking ASMR script written by Yuzuki Choco!
録りましたよ、チョコのASMRボイス！
I've recorded them, Choco's ASMR voices!
今回ね耳なめの方は、3つございます！
This time, there are three ear-licking scenarios!
1つ目が、『とろけるチョコレート』。
The first one is 'Melt-in-your-mouth Chocolate'.
いや、こちらはね、あーちょっと、皆様がご想像してるより、ちょっとあの、あの、エッチかもしれないんですけど、
Well, this one is... maybe a bit more 'erotic' than you imagine.
ま、配信ではね、絶対できないボイスとなっておりますので、是非ともね皆様、ご購入して聴いてみてください！
It's a voice I definitely can't do on stream, so please buy it and give it a listen!
そして、もう1つが、『残業後のご褒美デザート』ということで、こちらはねチョコとの同棲シチュエーションとなっております！
And another one is 'Reward Dessert after Overtime'. This is a cohabitation situation with Choco!
はい。チョコが残業してきて帰ってきた時の、うーん、ま、
Yes. It's when Choco comes back from working overtime. Hmm, well,
デザートはチョコなのか、君なのか、どっちなんだろうね？ ま、ちょっと聴いてみてよ！
is the dessert Choco or you? I wonder which? Please give it a listen!
そしてそして！『年下幼馴染のツンデレバレンタイン』ということで、
And then! 'Younger Childhood Friend's Tsundere Valentine'.
今回はね聴いている君たちが、ちょっと隣の家のお兄ちゃんになった気分で聴いてみてください！
This time, imagine you're the older brother next door while listening!
こちらもね、耳なめボイスとなっておりますが、なんとこちら、
This is also an ear-licking voice, and,
ドMの方は絶対に聴いていただけたら、ちょっとニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います！
if you're a masochist, I think you'll definitely be smiling while listening!
はい！そしてそして！フルセットをご購入の方！フルセット特典！
Yes! And! For those who purchase the full set! Full set bonus!
今回はなんと初めて、チェキ風ブロマイドカードになりました！
For the first time, it's a Cheki-style bromide card!
ちょっとこちらね、数量限定で直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージが入っております！
This one is limited in quantity and includes a handwritten autograph and a foil-stamped message!
カキカキしちゃうよ！通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サインと複製メッセージが入ります！
I'll be writing them! The regular version has a foil-stamped signature and message!
そしてね、特典がもう1つ！フルセット購入特典として、『焼きもちのギュッ』ASMRボイスが入っております！
And there's one more bonus! As a full set purchase bonus, the 'Jealous Hug' ASMR voice is included!
いや、こちらはね、ちょっとあの甘々のギュッボイスなので、
Well, this is a very sweet 'hug' voice.
ま、ちょっと普段はチョコ嫉妬しないんですけど、ちょっとま、何に嫉妬してるかは聴いてからのお楽しみなんですけど、
Choco doesn't usually get jealous, but you'll have to listen to find out what she's jealous of.
ちょっとぜひぜひ、ニヤニヤしながら聴いといてください！ぜひ手に入れてください！
Please listen with a grin on your face! Please get your hands on it!
そしてそして！重大告知！2つ目は、こちら！
And then! Major Announcement! The second one is this!
「…ねえ、ちょこたち もう二度と会えないの？」
"...Hey, Choco and the others... Can we never meet again?"
「不思議ね キミの言葉を聞くと なんだか元気が出てきちゃう」
"It's strange. When I hear your words, I somehow feel energized."
「ちょっ…し、しかたないわね 少しの間よ」
"Wait... I-I guess it can't be helped. Just for a little while."
「ちょこのことをもっともっと、大好きになってほしい」
"I want you to love Choco more and more."
「もう一度、会いたいよ。」
"I want to see you again."
「暗い感情も、孤独な気持ちも… こが全て食べてあげるわ。」
"Dark emotions, lonely feelings... I'll eat them all for you."
「ちょこが小悪魔なの…」
"Because Choco is a little devil..."
「ねえ、もしよければキミに… ちょこの思い出し話、聞いてほしい。」
"Hey, if you'd like... I want you to hear Choco's nostalgic stories."
「The Beginning」 12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース ＆ 連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
"The Beginning": 12 consecutive months of original song releases & linked voice drama project start.
1 3/15 から毎月15日0時 オリジナル楽曲リリース
1. Original song release on the 15th of every month at midnight starting 3/15.
豪華アーティスト参加
Featuring gorgeous artists.
癒月ちょことあなたのストーリーを辿った 全12話のボイスドラマ
A 12-episode voice drama following the story of Yuzuki Choco and you.
「The Beginning」 project 始動！
"The Beginning" project launch!
はーい！というわけで！
Yes! So!
はーい、癒月ちょこ。
Yes, Yuzuki Choco here.
2月15日からオリジナル楽曲12曲連続リリースが決定しました！
Starting February 15th, we've decided to release 12 consecutive original songs!
【The Beginning】
2月15日からオリジナル楽曲12曲連続リリース
(毎月15日0時リリース)
[The Beginning]
12 consecutive original song releases starting Feb 15
(Released on the 15th of every month at midnight)
しかも、こちら、なんとオリ曲に
And not only that, but these original songs...
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが一緒にリリースされます！
...will be released together with story-linked voice dramas!
楽曲に連動したストーリーのボイスドラマ発売
豪華アーティストが参加
Story-linked voice dramas to be released with songs
Featuring renowned artists
いや、こちらね、約第1話から
Well, here, from about Episode 1...
12話まで1曲ずつに連動して
...to Episode 12, each song will be linked...
ボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててください！
...to a voice drama, so please look forward to it!
そして今回はね、その記念すべき
And today, I'm going to perform...
1曲目をこれから披露したいと思います！
...that memorable first song!
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
「キミの秒針」。
"Kimi no Byoushin."
戻れないからまた
Because I can't go back
あなた 愛しさが募る
my love for you grows deeper
君に 会いたいよ
I want to see you
キミの秒針
作詞：マオ(SID) 作曲：御恵明希(SID)
Kimi no Byoushin
Lyrics: Mao (SID) Composition: Aki Mimie (SID)
君から受け取った 壊れそうなストーリー
The fragile story I received from you
どこまでも広がる 蒼い空
The blue sky stretching endlessly
変わらない毎日も 色のない夢も
The unchanging days, the colorless dreams
手放して 始めよう
Let's let go and begin
不安の夜を数え
Counting the anxious nights
泣きながら迎えた 明日でもいい
Even if it's a tomorrow met while crying
時計の針のように 刻んだ思い出たち
Like the hands of a clock, the memories we've etched
広げた
spread out
戻れないからまた
because I can't go back
愛しさが募る
my love grows deeper
君に会いたいよ
I want to see you
二人で暖めた 大切なストーリー
The precious story we warmed together
遠くまで続いた 果てない道
The endless road that continued far away
「疲れたら代わるから」 そう言ってくれた
"I'll take over if you're tired," you said
優しさに触れて見えた
I could see it when I felt your kindness
受け入れてくれたこと
That you accepted me
忘れない 嬉しくて満ちた日
I won't forget the days filled with joy
雨上がりの胸に 架かった虹のように
Like a rainbow arched in my heart after the rain
綺麗な君からの言葉
The beautiful words from you
ひとつひとつが 今も宝物
Each and every one is still a treasure
支えてくれたから 輝ける
Because you supported me, I can shine
この気持ち 届けよう
I'll deliver these feelings
時計の針のように 刻んだ思い出たち
Like the hands of a clock, the memories we've etched
広げた 戻れないからまた
Spread out; because I can't go back
愛しさが募る 君に会いたいよ
My love grows deeper, I want to see you
雨上がりの胸に 架かった虹のように
Like a rainbow arched in my heart after the rain
綺麗な君からの言葉
The beautiful words from you
ひとつひとつが 今も宝物
Each and every one is still a treasure
はい、ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Alright, so, how did everyone like it?
今回の新曲「君の秒針」は、シドのマヲ様が作詞、
My new song, "Kimi no Byoushin," was written by Shido Mawo,
そして、二目極アツ様が作曲、編曲、
and composed and arranged by Nimegumi Atsushi.
そして編曲にはなんと加藤貴之様も加わっていただきました！
And Kato Takayoshi also joined for the arrangement!
いや、今回はボイスドラマ連動企画の第一弾として、
This time, as the first part of a voice drama tie-in project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、珠玉の楽曲に仕上がっております。
it's a masterpiece that serves as the theme song for the entire story.
まぁ、ドラマの鍵となるね、「秒針」というメタファーにも、ぜひ注目してください。
Please also pay attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which is key to the drama.
シドさんだけではなく、この後ね、豪華アーティストの皆様にも、たくさん書いていただいたので、
Not just Shido-san, but many other wonderful artists have also written for us,
皆様、リリースお楽しみに。
so everyone, please look forward to the releases.
こちらの「君の秒針」は、各音楽サイトは、ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、
For "Kimi no Byoushin," it'll be a little while before it hits music sites,
3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます。
but it's scheduled to be released at midnight on March 15th.
まぁ、ちょっとね、公開まで時間が空くから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してみてください。
Since there's a bit of time until then, please watch this stream over and over again.
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it a lot!
そしてそして、
And also, and also,
MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしててくださーい。
the MV will be released later as well, so please look forward to it.
ということで、今日のチョコの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
So, how was Choco's birthday live today?
まぁ、この後はすぐに、
Well, right after this,
ちょっと冒頭、最初の方でお披露目した、
as I showed at the very beginning,
ノエルちゃんとラミィたんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があって、
the MV for "Hatsukoi Daisensou" with Noel-chan and Lamy-tan will be released.
その後、メン限で、ちょっとライブと撮影会の続きとか、
After that, on my membership-only stream, we'll continue with the live performance and photoshoot,
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
and do some situation dramas that can only be seen there,
ぜひぜひ、気になる人は見に行ってください。
so if you're interested, please come and watch.
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう。
Well then, I'll see you all later.
おつかれーと。
Otsukarei-to.
はむっ！
Ham!
君の秒針
Kimi no Byoushin (Your Second Hand)
♥ このあとのメン限 ♥
アフターライブ、特別撮影会、シチュエーションドラマ2本
♥ Membership Stream After This ♥
After-live, Special Photoshoot, 2 Situation Dramas